[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Oh, we had some good times, Trashy.
哦，我们度过了一些美好时光，Trashy。
But you're gonna love the dump.
但你一定会喜欢这个垃圾场的。
You'll make
so many trashy new friends.
你会让
这么多垃圾新朋友。
Ooh.
哦。
[laughs]
[笑]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
I'm gonna miss you.
我会想念你的。
Huh?
啊？
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
Hi, Mrs. Puff!
嗨，泡芙女士！
Ah!
啊!
I'm not here!
我不在！
Oops, my mistake.
哎呀，我的错误。
Hi, Plankton!
嗨，浮游生物！
Hi, Bubble Bass!
嗨，泡泡巴斯！
Hi, Mr. Mailman!
嗨，邮递员先生！
[together] We're not here.
[在一起]我们不在这里。
Huh, maybe I need glasses.
呃，也许我需要戴眼镜。
[hums]
[哼哼]
[knocking]
[敲门声]
Fellow sponge sufferers,
海绵宝宝们，
the 431st We Hate SpongeBob Club
第431届我们讨厌海绵宝宝俱乐部
will now come to order.
现在将来订购。
And now our motto...
现在我们的座右铭...
all: We don't mean SpongeBob
any harm.
全部：我们不是指海绵宝宝
任何伤害。
We just can't stand him.
我们就是受不了他。
Does anyone have any
new sponge-pain
有谁有吗
新海绵疼痛
they would like to share?
他们愿意分享吗？
- How much time do you have?
- I do!
- 你有多少时间？
- 我愿意！
- Oh, yes, I do.
- I have to unwrap my package
- 哦，是的，我愿意。
- 我必须打开我的包裹
of pain.
- [laughing]
的痛苦。
- [笑]
Huh?
Hold that agony.
啊？
忍住那种痛苦吧。
Hello, Squidward!
你好，章鱼哥！
Proceed.
继续。
Ahem, I have some misfortune
to share.
咳咳，我有些不幸
分享。
The chair recognizes
sufferer Puff.
主席认识到
受苦者泡芙。
Please receive
the Speaking Sponge.
请接收
会说话的海绵
It all began last week.
both: ♪ La-la-la ♪
这一切都始于上周。
两者：♪ 啦啦啦 ♪
I was enjoying one
of my favorite things,
我很享受其中一个
我最喜欢的东西，
awarding a student
their driver's license.
奖励学生
他们的驾驶执照。
You've passed
your driver's exam, Bertie.
你已经通过了
你的驾驶考试，伯蒂。
- [gasps]
- Congratulations.
- [喘气]
- 恭喜。
I couldn't have done it
without you, Mrs. Puff.
我做不到
没有你，普芙夫人。
[laughs]
I bet you can teach anyone.
[笑]
我打赌你可以教任何人。
[laughs]
Oh.
[笑]
哦。
Hmm?
- [cackling]
唔？
- [咯咯笑]
Almost anyone.
几乎任何人。
- Nice license.
- [whimpers]
- 好的许可证。
- [呜咽]
Can I touch it?
我可以摸一下吗？
[laughs]
- Ew, gross!
[笑]
- 呃，恶心！
[straining]
[紧张]
Ow!
[loud crash]
噢！
[巨响]
Well,
looks like you have an opening
嗯，
看起来你有空缺
in your schedule, Mrs. Puff.
在你的日程安排中，帕芙女士。
I tried to leave,
我试图离开，
but we all know
there is no escape from...
但我们都知道
无法逃脱……
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
[cackling]
[咯咯笑]
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
[engine revving]
[发动机转速]
Ah! Ooh.
啊!哦。
Accelerate safely into traffic.
加速安全进入交通。
[engine roars]
[发动机轰鸣声]
Now for a 360-point turn!
现在来个 360 度大转弯！
[cackling]
[咯咯笑]
Ahh!
啊！
[tires screeching]
[轮胎的尖叫声]
Oops. Almost ran a stop sign.
哎呀。差点就跑到停车标志了。
Whoa!
哇！
Ohh-ohh-ohh!
哦哦哦！
Ahh!
啊！
Oof.
钱币。
SpongeBob destroyed
my beautiful school.
海绵宝宝被摧毁
我美丽的学校。
Just like last week!
就像上周一样！
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
It's okay.
没关系。
We're here for you.
我们随时为您服务。
Who would like to share next?
接下来谁愿意分享？
I would.
我会的。
I'd like to share a hug.
我想分享一个拥抱。
Looks like you could use
a stamp!
看起来你可以使用
一张邮票！
I believe that I am next
我相信我就是下一个
in the roundelay.
在圆形延迟中。
My speaking sponge, please.
我的会说话的海绵，请。
Hmm.
唔。
I was at the Krusty Krab
to grab a light snack
我在蟹堡王店
吃点小吃
between first and second lunch.
第一顿午餐和第二顿午餐之间。
Order up, oh, valued customer.
尊敬的顾客，赶快下单吧。
Ah, finally sustenance
for my starving stomach.
啊终于有食粮了
为了我饥饿的胃。
I hope it's perfect.
我希望它是完美的。
Ahh...
啊...
- [gasps]
- Huh?
- [喘气]
- 啊？
It's not perfect!
这并不完美！
It's too greasy!
太油腻了！
[groans]
Hmm.
[呻吟]
嗯。
And this fry
isn't greasy enough!
还有这个炒菜
还不够油腻！
Try as I might... [coughs]
尽我所能...[咳嗽]
SpongeBob would not let me
consume a single calorie.
海绵宝宝不让我
消耗一卡路里。
I tried to take a sip of soda
to slake my thirst.
我试着喝了一口苏打水
解渴。
[gasps]
[喘气]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[slurping]
[发出声音]
Bleh.
布莱赫。
Not fizzy enough!
不够泡啊！
[growls]
[咆哮]
That perforated pest wouldn't
let me taste a morsel
那个穿孔害虫不会
让我尝一口
of Krabby Patty.
蟹黄派蒂。
Ahh!
啊！
Give me back my patty,
you festering fusspot!
把我的肉饼还给我
你这个溃烂的小题大做！
[gasps]
I can't.
[喘气]
我不能。
[growls]
[咆哮]
[panting] The sesame seeds
are misaligned,
[喘气] 芝麻
未对准，
and the lettuce
has too many wrinkles!
和生菜
皱纹太多了！
The tomato has lost its sheen!
西红柿失去了光泽！
Let me eat,
you insufferable interrupter!
让我吃，
你这个令人难以忍受的干扰者！
Victory is mine!
胜利是我的！
[gulps]
[吞咽]
[cackling]
[咯咯笑]
[groans]
[呻吟]
A-ooga!
啊啊啊！
[cackling]
[咯咯笑]
[munching]
[咀嚼]
A tad spongy, but not bad.
有点海绵状，但还不错。
[stomach rumbles]
Ooh.
[肚子咕咕叫]
哦。
That fry cook has given me
a slight case of...
那个炒菜厨师给了我
一个轻微的案例...
[gulps]
indigestion.
[吞咽]
消化不良。
[stomach rumbles]
[肚子咕咕叫]
Oh.
- [grunting]
哦。
- [咕哝]
I shall let no customer eat
a less-than-perfect patty.
我不会让任何顾客吃饭
不太完美的肉饼
Oh.
哦。
Ahh.
啊。
I forgot my hat.
我忘记带帽子了。
Ahh!
啊！
[gulps]
[吞咽]
That squishy simpleton
left my navel in knots.
那个软软的傻瓜
让我的肚脐打结。
[grunting]
You call that suffering?
[咕噜声]
你管这叫苦？
I'll tell you
a truly terrifying tale.
我告诉你
一个真正可怕的故事。
It was a dark and spongy night.
那是一个又黑又松软的夜晚。
I was working peacefully
in my lab
我平静地工作
在我的实验室
on my newest invention to, uh,
help fishkind?
关于我的最新发明，呃，
帮助鱼类？
Yeah, that's it.
是的，就是这样。
Yes, my terrible toilet paper
will wipe Bikini Bottom
是的，我糟糕的卫生纸
会擦拭比基尼泳裤
off the face of the ocean!
离开海洋！
[laughs]
Plus it's quilted.
[笑]
而且它是绗缝的。
[cackling]
[咯咯笑]
- [laughing]
- Huh?
- [笑]
- 啊？
Eh.
[cackling]
呃。
[咯咯笑]
[laughing]
[笑]
Why does something always
ruin a good evil laugh?
为什么有些事总是
毁掉善恶的笑声？
- [laughing]
- Huh?
- [笑]
- 啊？
But then I saw it.
但后来我看到了。
A wild SpongeBob had gotten
into my lab.
野生海绵宝宝得到了
[cawing]
[啼叫]
Karen!
凯伦！
It got in again!
又进来了！
Did you leave
the window open again?
你离开了吗
窗户又打开了吗？
[cawing]
[啼叫]
Ah!
It's in my mainframe!
啊!
它在我的主机里！
- [squawks]
- Oh, you dirty bird.
- [嘎嘎声]
-哦，你这只肮脏的鸟。
Get down from there!
Git!
从那里下来！
吉特！
[cawing]
[啼叫]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
[squawks]
[嘎嘎声]
Ahh!
啊！
Come on, Lazybones.
加油吧，懒骨头们。
Sweep it out the door.
扫出门去。
[groaning]
[呻吟]
[babbling]
[胡说]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Ahh!
- 哇，哇，哇！
- 啊！
Whoa-oh-oh!
哇哦哦！
Ah!
啊!
[both groan]
[两人都呻吟]
[laughing]
[笑]
[straining]
[紧张]
He's locked us out!
他把我们锁在门外了！
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
[thunder booming]
[雷霆轰鸣]
So if you hear
that horrible sound
所以如果你听到
那可怕的声音
of a SpongeBob, just run.
海绵宝宝，跑吧。
[groans]
[呻吟]
[muffled]
Run for your lives.
[低声]
为你的生命而奔跑。
[babbling]
[all gasp]
[胡言乱语]
[全都喘气]
Calm down.
冷静下来。
My AC is just acting up again.
我的空调又开始工作了。
- Whew.
- Thank Neptune.
- 呼。
- 感谢海王星。
You think you all have it bad?
你以为你们都过得不好吗？
Wait until you hear my tale
of spongy terror
等你听我的故事
海绵状的恐怖
in real time.
实时。
Three, two, one.
三、二、一。
[doorbell rings]
Hmm.
[门铃响]
嗯。
He had arrived.
他已经到了。
[eerie music]
[怪异音乐]
all: Huh?
全体：啊？
But there was no one there.
但那里没有人。
Perhaps it was nothing.
也许这没什么。
Or was SpongeBob already
in the house?
或者海绵宝宝已经
在房子里？
♪ ♪
♪♪
Could I borrow a cup
of saltwater?
可以借个杯子吗
盐水？
[sighs]
[叹气]
Here.
这里。
Of course, the saltwater
was just a ruse
当然，盐水
只是一个诡计
to come inside uninvited.
不请自来地进来。
Ooh.
[all gasp]
哦。
[全都喘气]
Are you having a party?
你要开派对吗？
Naturally,
SpongeBob lost no time
自然地，
海绵宝宝不失时机
annoying everyone in the room.
惹恼了房间里的每个人。
Hi, Mrs. Puff.
嗨，普芙女士。
I can't wait until
my next lesson.
我等不及了
我的下一课。
Eww.
呃。
Mailman, I gotta tell ya,
邮递员，我得告诉你，
every package from you
is a special delivery.
你的每一个包裹
是特殊快递。
Let's catch up soon, huh?
我们快点追上吧？
- [groans]
- Looking fit, Bubble Bass.
- [呻吟]
- 看起来很健康，泡泡巴斯。
Been pumping the iron, huh?
一直在打铁吧？
And, Plankton,
has anyone ever told you
还有，浮游生物，
有没有人告诉过你
that you have the loveliest eye?
你有最可爱的眼睛吗？
Of course,
if SpongeBob was around,
当然，
如果海绵宝宝在身边
his pointy pink pal
couldn't be far behind.
他尖尖的粉红色朋友
也不甘落后。
Ah.
啊。
You're out of punch.
你没力气了。
[growls]
[咆哮]
Don't worry, Squidward.
I'll mix up a batch
别担心，章鱼哥。
我会混合一批
of my special pineapple punch.
我特制的菠萝潘趣酒。
[growls]
[咆哮]
It's homemade.
这是自制的。
Made out of the walls
of my home.
由墙壁制成
我家的。
[laughs]
[笑]
Oof!
钱币！
And no SpongeBob story
would be complete
也没有海绵宝宝的故事
将会完成
without him destroying something.
没有他破坏什么东西。
I've got pineapple punch!
我有菠萝宾治！
Whoa!
哇！
[electricity crackling]
[电力噼啪声]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
Oops.
哎呀。
The end.
结束。
[siren wailing]
[警笛哀号]
Where are we gonna finish
our club meeting now?
我们要在哪里结束
我们的俱乐部现在开会吗？
Ahem.
咳咳。
I know a place
you could have your meeting.
我知道一个地方
你可以开会了。
[all groan]
[全都呻吟]
Who's ready for hors d'oeuvres?
谁准备好开胃小菜了？
Watch out for the...
留意...
[gulps]
[吞咽]
- Toothpicks.
- Phooey.
- 牙签。
- 噗。
We're all out
of speaking sponges.
我们都出去了
会说话的海绵。
Oh, no, you're not.
哦，不，你不是。
There's one left.
还剩一张了
[babbling]
[胡说]
And I was...
[coughs]
而我当时...
[咳嗽]
Coughing up his mail for weeks.
他的邮件被咳了好几个星期。
[coughs]
[咳嗽]
[breezy upbeat music]
[轻快欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
I declare this meeting
我宣布这次会议
of the We Hate SpongeBob Club adjourned.
我们讨厌海绵宝宝俱乐部休会了。
Bang.
砰。
[groans]
[呻吟]